(Sheldon:)...where when a hunter flaunts his success
to the rest of the village...
(Sheldon:)...they kill him and drive away evil spirits
with a drum made of his skin.
(Sheldon:)Superstitious nonsense, of course,
but one can see their point.
(Penny(bringing another grasshopper):)Here you go, Raj.
You might wanna drink this one slowly.
(Raj:)Okay. So Saturday night,
can I count on my posse?
(Howard:)Gee, I'd love to, Raj, but I can't make it.
(Raj:)Oh, okay. Leonard?
(Leonard:)Well, uh...
No, I could... No.
(Leonard:)- Sheldon?
- I can make it, but I won't.
- What are you talking about?
- The reception for my article on Saturday.
(Penny:)You guys aren't going?
(Penny:)I can't believe you. Raj is celebrating
a tremendous accomplishment.
You're not gonna be there?
(Sheldon:)A tremendous accomplishment would be
if the planetary body he discovered...
(Sheldon:)...were plummeting toward Earth
and he exploded it with his mind.